[
   { 
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 79 and height 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "79.0",
      "options": [
        "79.0",
        "76.5",
        "83.0",
        "81.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 43 and height 59?",
      "correctAnswer": "1268.5",
      "options": [
        "1272.5",
        "1266.0",
        "1268.5",
        "1271.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 49 and height 21?",
      "correctAnswer": "514.5",
      "options": [
        "514.5",
        "517.0",
        "512.0",
        "518.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 4 and height 86?",
      "correctAnswer": "172.0",
      "options": [
        "174.5",
        "176.0",
        "169.5",
        "172.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 68 and height 82?",
      "correctAnswer": "2788.0",
      "options": [
        "2788.0",
        "2792.0",
        "2785.5",
        "2790.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 62 and height 39?",
      "correctAnswer": "1209.0",
      "options": [
        "1213.0",
        "1206.5",
        "1211.5",
        "1209.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 7 and height 33?",
      "correctAnswer": "115.5",
      "options": [
        "113.0",
        "119.5",
        "118.0",
        "115.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 30 and height 14?",
      "correctAnswer": "210.0",
      "options": [
        "207.5",
        "210.0",
        "212.5",
        "214.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 86 and height 89?",
      "correctAnswer": "3827.0",
      "options": [
        "3824.5",
        "3831.0",
        "3827.0",
        "3829.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 7 and height 85?",
      "correctAnswer": "297.5",
      "options": [
        "301.5",
        "300.0",
        "295.0",
        "297.5"
      ]
    }
]